{
    "id": "23b21a77490e4f078e9b36c4171b9e1b",
    "title": "Most And Most Of",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………… cheese is made from milk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "Most of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4ad5ba4f3c004a01a75a536dcd7dca81"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. England was under water.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "Most of",
                "Either could be here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1814a7944da54bd080da86650146f265"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… people like movies.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "Most of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fc2fd52264154f4192ac44213469ea33"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… people in Switzerland can speak French.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "Most of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cae095f035a04f6895f10e7f281e0bc0"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has eaten …………………. that cake.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "most",
                "most of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e686eda194a24cbfbac8de7795ff4ac2"
        },
        {
            "question": "She wasn’t as intelligent as her sisters, but she was …………………. beautiful.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "most",
                "most of",
                "the most"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "654f387d91b94d188012f56784e5b300"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. my friends are non-smokers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "Most of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f9d91bdde41c4e179ac4b2c7f8c09972"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… . us were impressed with the plan.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "Most of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "98a0bd6894184df4a832a6610683e2d9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which country produces the ………………… milk?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "most",
                "most of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "30147deef07447508c84eba717e0dd64"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. them were uneducated.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "Most of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c3f04d04382f4cf7998433fcb619e2f1"
        }
    ]
}